Okay, wow that's stretchy. Hi everyone, welcome to another video here on my channel. Today I'm going to show you something I found. It is not really known in Europe by now. It's rather, I don't know, Asian sports and swimwear.
and it's going to be a lot of shimmery spandex outfits. I have six items to show you and
yeah, let's start right with the first one because I'm curious myself.
I'm packing the first one. It looks super short from the legs but haha, it's super stretchy.
try. Okay I managed to stretch everything so much that it fits. So the legs are kind
of long enough. I'm just realizing that there's a lot of tension on the straps
here. So it may be a bit too short but I already guessed that. Although I'm kind of
surprised that it is so comfortable, nevertheless, because it's really super
stretchy. What can I say? It reminds me of a hybrid between, I don't know, a swimsuit
and a jumpsuit with the racer back and the cut here in the legs. It's definitely
something unique. I paired it with a simple pair of perms and yeah of course
it's missing something for the arms but kind of funny. I promised you some color
and here we go. It's going to be purple. I noticed that during the making a latex
bodysuit video a lot of you said that you actually like the purple latex so
maybe you like this purple slightly shiny whatever spandex fabric as well it
actually looks quite long and there is a second part also purple it's a leggings
or rather a tie because there are socks integrated okay so this is what I was
talking about in the beginning when I said that it's a thing somewhere not in
Germany I can tell you that and not in Europe as far as I know but yeah what do
you think I think it is a bit too much purple although the leggings are super
comfortable because it's so stretchy and smooth and I can't stop touching it
because it's so smooth. You may not guess it but I'm currently wearing size extra large because
you can't compare them with European sizes. They have their own sizing schema and every piece has
its own measurements and its own starting size. So this is extra large. The other one before was
medium and I think medium was the smallest size I ordered in general. So
just look at the measurements and not at the sizes as a size but at the like
numbers of the measurements and I have to say the stuff I ordered according to
the measurements it fits so you can really work with that. It definitely is a
fun combination with the purple and the bright green and black although I'm not
sure if I would leave the house dressed like that. Would you? Tell me in the
comments. A swimsuit! I'm actually surprised how good this fits. Let's see
with the back. And the length is okay as well. I'm wearing size large so again
check the measurements and I didn't think I could squeeze into this when I
saw it but yeah it works. The brand is called LeoHex by the way you can check
them out I'll link their Aliexpress store below and they have a YouTube
channel as well with cool videos so have a look there and thanks to LeoHex for
supporting me I have a lot of fun here. Now I only need a beach and good warm
whether to wear this one outside I would do it no problem you know the first time
I saw this bodysuit was at a video here on YouTube by Tsutsika and she wore it to
beach I mean okay she lives in Australia so that's so cool I would love to go
there or travel or whatever but since I'm living in Germany and it's March and
and rather cold outside and I don't have a beach here,
I thought I'll jump into the bathtub and try it.
Oh, it's so warm.
So weird to wear clothes while sitting in the bathtub.
Okay, it does not really feel like a swimsuit.
I mean still like fabric which I'm wearing so it feels like I'm sitting with clothes in a bathtub
which is kind of weird but it's also fun I don't mind it's missing the feeling of a swimsuit
and it just fits like normal clothing which is kind of weird but uh yeah still like the look of
it and another disadvantage I heard of when I asked Tsutsika if I can use her video to show to
she said that it gets really really hot in the sunlight and I think due to the
PVC fabric you're going to sweat a lot so maybe not the best choice for beach
day okay next is a long sleeve and a pretty cool color so I'm really looking
forward to try this on. It's size large again. Alright this is cool I like it. I
would wear it on a daily basis if the arms would be longer. Bummer again. But I
already said that I really like the color. It's a cool tone down blue and it's
super comfortable. The fabric really feels super nice. I paired it with a simple jeans
to create a more normal look. More normal than a purple one anyway. And yeah, as with all the
other fabrics from Leo Hacks, this is again super stretchy here. That was my selection.
and then leo hacks also packed something in this color and in this size it's like oh my god how
how how just how should that work it's size large it's in europe size large it would be not
like this but this would be rather extra extra small or something super weird uh i don't know
if I'm going to fit into this one. I'll have to try. Wish me luck. It fits, kinda. I mean,
the arms are super long, I'm surprised, and it does fit, but I have to say the extra large, the
purple one was way more comfortable because it is a bit short. And yeah, there's a two-way zipper,
like what?
Uh yeah
Anyway, not not sure
about this color in general, but that was super fun. I hope you had fun as well
leave a comment and hit the subscribe button
And click on the thumbs up have a look at the leo hacks youtube. I'll link it and uh, yeah
Have a nice day. See you around